Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Tapes
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-1)
    Showtime Networks, Inc. Mastergate Clips, CBS Sunday Morning 11/1/92; Entertainment Tonight 11/1/92; CNN Showbiz 10/30/92; E! Entertainment 10/28/92.
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-1)
    Rollins & Joffe Imagination Prod. Final Edited Sweetend Master Viewing Dub Stereo, 10/25/92
  - MERCER AND THE MOVIES (Box Ser. T-1)
    Waldorf Astoria, NYC, November 9, 1987. Includes note resound quality of the tape.
  - TELEVISION (Box Ser. T-1)
    Larry Gelbart Clips. Vid-Edit, Los Angeles. n.d.
  - BARBARIANS DAYS (Box Ser. T-2)
    Nos 1-3. n.d.
  - CITY OF ANGELS (Box Ser. T-2)
    Opening night reviews and reports, n.d.
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-2)
    Raw footage, Video D Studios, Inc. N.Y.C., n.d.
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-2)
    Mastergate # 2, n.d.
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-2)
    First Cut View Copy, 9/22/92.
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-2)
    TV News, 3 minutes, n.d. Video D Studios, NYC
  - MASTERGATE (Box Ser. T-2)
    MVP Films, The Golden Group. "What Did the President Know", 10/2/89.
  - PETER AND THE WOLF (Box Ser. T-2)
    Studio Run Thru, 10/22/91
  - PETER AND THE WOLF (Box Ser. T-2)
    ABT, October 1991
  - PETER AND THE WOLF
    ABT, 1992
  - CITY OF ANGELS
    C-D of the Original London Cast Recording.
  - EVENING WITH LARRY GELBART (Box Ser. T-3)
    Hosted by Keith Berwick, March 26, 1987, DGA. The Academy of Television Arts and Sciences. 2 audio cassettes.
  - ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE (Box Ser. T-3)
    [9] Songs from … Music and Lyrics by Maury Yeston. 1/4 inch tape.
  - TOOTSIE (Box Ser. T-4)
    30audio cassettes of conversations Hoffman-Ashby-Gelbart--Pollack. January-December 1981.
  - BLAME IT ON RIO
    Audio cassette. "I must be doing something right".
  - CITY OF ANGELS (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassette: Act II of original Tokyo cast.
  - JAZZ BABIES (Box Ser. T-5)
    8 audio cassettes, January - December 1984, many with Peggy Gilbert. December 6 tapes include Patrick Palmer, Charles Milhaupt, Meeting to Discuss, Revisions on First Draft.
  - PETER AND THE WOLF (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassette: LSO- Previns. n.d.
  - PETER AND THE WOLF (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassette, note attached "Not good, but with video, it might help."
  - STEVE ALLEN SHOW (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassettes with Larry Gelbart, 12/14/87.
  - STEVE ALLEN SHOW
    2 audio cassettes, WNEW w/ Larry Gelbart, Part I and Part 2, 9/24/87.
  - UNITED STATES (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassette: Greenfield, CBS- May 4.
  - UNITED STATES (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassette: Interview on Public Radio, n.d.
  - UNITED STATES (Box Ser. T-5)
    Audio cassettes for episodes # 1,2,4,7,8.9.10,13,14,15,18,20, and Theme.
  - DEATH IS FOR SUCKERS
    10 audio cassettes, 6 dated May 1987 (Cy, David, Larry, and Act I ), 1 dated 1985 (Larry Cy Coleman), 1 dated 1984 (Larry, Cy Coleman), 2 undated.
  - FILM AT 11 (Box Ser. T-6)
    Audio cassette. Larry Gelbart and Arthur Penn, 6/5/79.
  - JACK OAKIE MEMORIAL LECTURE
    2 Audio cassettes. "Comedy for the Screen", 11/12/81.
  - MICHAEL JACKSON SHOW (Box Ser. T-6)
    Audio cassette. KABC, 3/2/83.
  - PAY THE MILLION DOLLARS (Box Ser. T-6)
    Audio cassette. Sketch, 1983 or 1982.
  - 57TH ANNUAL ACADEMY AWARDS
    Audio cassette. Five nominated songs.
  - AFTERMASH
    Audio cassette. Research, 1983.
  - AFTERMASH
    Audio cassette. Final 1984.
  - CBS AFFILIATES. (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. "From Century Plaza", 1973.
  - CHARLES CHAMPLIN (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. "Tribute to Ross MacDonald". n.d.
  - CONQUERING HERO
    Audio cassette.
  - JACK O'BRIAN
    Audio cassette. O'Brian with Gelbart, 12/5/78.
  - JACK O'BRIAN SHOW (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. WOR (Radio), NYC 10/1/84.
  - LARRY GELBART (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. Unidentified event, n.d.
  - LARRY GELBART (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. "Tootsie, M.A.S.H. and me" Santa Barbara Writers Conference". n.d. [on reverse side of tape with CHARLES CHAMPLIN].
  - M*A*S*H (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. Songs :Five Gold Stars", "Big Mac Is Comin". Loudon Wainwright III. n.d.
  - M*A*S*H (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. Reynolds/Gelbart/Carol Hemongway, Jan. 1976.
  - M*A*S*H
    Audio cassette. MASH segment, on "All Things Considered", 1/28/83.
  - MOVIE MOVIE (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. Martin ….., Harry Handlim, Rebecca York, 12/6/78.
  - NOTHING BUT A LADY (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. L. G and Everett Greenbaum. interview with Miss Alvernel (?). Research, 1982.
  - ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE
    Audio cassette. Marked "Yeston". n.d.
  - OVERNIGHTS
    Audio Cassette. Presentation 5/26/87.
  - SCREENING ROOM SICKNESS (Box Ser. T-7)
    Audio cassette. L.G. notes for review of Ernest Lehman's book, 1982.
  - BALLROOM (Box Ser. T-8)
    3 audio cassettes. n.d.
  - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (Box Ser. T-8)
    Two audio cassettes. Read by the authors Bryan Burroughs and John Helyar. Harper Audio edition.
  - CAMBODIA PROJECT (Box Ser. T-8)
    Three audio cassettes. "Characters:, 12/16/79; "Outline", 12/16/79; Arthur Penn 5/28/80.
  - CITY OF ANGELS
    Audio cassette. Original Tokyo cast. Act I and II.
  - DUSTIN HOFFMAN (Box Ser. T-8)
    Two audio cassettes. "Soap interview", n.d. "Dustin/Susan Pratt" 4/3/81.
  - GULLIVER'S TRAVELS (Box Ser. T-8)
    Three audio cassettes: "Voyage to Lilliput" and Voyage to Brobdingnag. Sir John Gielgud, Music by Patrick Williams, narrated by Larry Gelbart.
  - TOOTSIE
    Two audio cassettes. Tape # 31 and Log.
  - WRITERS' STRIKE
    Audio cassette. Live from Trumps", 3/16/85.
- Writings
  - Press, Writings, Miscellaneous (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Personal Primer (A), 1998 Mar 14 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Fade In, 1999 Sept - Oct (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Writings, 1997-1999 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Writings, 1998-1999 (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Dudley Moore Tribute, 2001 Apr (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - New Pieces, 2001-2002 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Essays, Press, Interviews (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Essays, Press, Interviews (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Essays, Press, 2000-2001 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Press, New Pieces, Miscellaneous (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 June - Oct (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - New Pieces, 2004 Feb - May (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - New Pieces (Folder 1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - New Pieces (Folder 2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles Library Reading, 2005 Nov (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - New Pieces, 2004 July - Nov (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - New Pieces and Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - New Pieces (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 Nov - 2005 Apr (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - New Pieces (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 Nov - 2005 Apr (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Huffington Post, 2005 May - June (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Cedars-Sinai Medical Center Celebration of George Burns 100th Birthday, 1996 Jan 16 (Box 316, Folder 7)
  - Humanitas Prize Luncheon Keynote Address, 1995 July 6 (Box 316, Folder 8)
  - Woody Allen, 1990 Mar 6 (Box 316, Folder 10)
  - New Pieces, 1999, 2006 (Box 321, Folder 6)
  - New Pieces, 2007 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - New Pieces, 2006 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Personal Primer (A), 1998 Mar (Box 323, Folder 4)